const quiz1data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "He ___ sing very well.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "can", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "may", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'can' to talk about someone's skill or general abilities."
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "Sally ___ come by car.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "can", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "may", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use 'may, might and could' to say that something is possible, but not certain."
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "You ___ stop at a red light.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "must", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'must' or 'need to' to say that it is necessary to do something."
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "__ you carry this bag for me, please?",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Would", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "Might", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'would' as a polite way of asking someone to do something."
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "Dennis ___ speak Spanish very well.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "can", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "may", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'can' to talk about someone's skill or general abilities."
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "I __ go to London next week. I haven't decided yet.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "must", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "might", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use 'may' and 'might' to talk about possible actions or happenings in the future."
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "They ___ be at the concert.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "might", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "can", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'may, might and could' to say that something is possible, but not certain."
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "John ___ swim.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "can't", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "may not", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'can' and 'can`t' to talk about someone's skill or general abilities."
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "___ you pass me the phone, please? ",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "May", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "Could", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "We use 'could' and 'would' as polite ways of telling or asking someone to do something. 'Can' and 'Will' are less polite."
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "It's getting cloudy. It ___ be start raining soon.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "must", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "should", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'must' to show we are sure something is true and we have reasons for our belief."
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "__ I buy a coffee for you?",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "Can", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "Must", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'can' to make offers."
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "It ___ be very cold here in winter.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "can", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "may", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use 'can' to make general statements about what is possible."
    },
  ]
export default quiz1data
